

SKILLS

- NUXT.JS
- VUE.JS
- VUEX
- BOOTSTRAP
- JAVASCRIPT
- GIT
- TAILWIND
- CSS
- HTML

Language

- English
- MALAYALAM
- TAMIL

Contact

- Bangalore
- +91 9633180504
- prathyushapachu985@gmail.com

PRATHYUSHA FRONT END DEVELOPER

About Me:

2+ years experienced front-end developer who is responsible for creating and implementing the visual and interactive elements of a website or application that users interact with directly. This includes developing user interface (UI) designs, layouts, and features using various programming languages, such as **Vue.js**, **Nuxt.js**, **HTML**, **CSS**, and **JavaScript**.

Work Experience:

Front end developer - Armino technologies Pvt Ltd Nov 2023 - Present

- Project: Online exam admin dashboard and web app.
- Creating Responsive Ui designs and dashboards using vue.js,
 Vuetify, Supabase.

Software Developer - ACEMERO TECHNOLOGIES PVT.LTD Dec 2021 - Oct 2023

 Junior Software Developer is specializing in front-end development. I experienced with all stages of the development cycle for dynamic web projects. Well-versed in numerous programming languages including Vuejs, Nuxt.js,Node.js, bootstrap tailwind, vuex, HTML5, JavaScript, CSS, and MySQL.
 Strong background in project management and customer relations.

Operating Engineer - MANDO AUTOMOTIVE INDIA LIMITED May 2019 - May 2020

 At Mando Automotive India Private Limited, Chennai – from June 2019 (A Joint venture of MANDO KOREA & Anand group INDIA) dealing with Hydraulic Brake Systems, Suspension Systems, EBS, Steering Systems and having Hyundai, Significant Achievement: Awarded as best CI team for 6 times in 2019. Worked as a member of the Continuous Improvement Team, the Best model work center, 5S award-winning team in 2019 by Kaizen.

LINKS

• LinkedIn:

https://www.linkedin.com/in/prathyu sha-pramod/

PROJECT

NUCLEUS

Skills Used: Nuxt.js, Vue.js,
 Javascript, Tailwind, HTML, CSS
 Role: Front-End Developer
 Description: Admin panel of an integrated social media
 application.

INTERNSHIP

Web Developer Trainee - BTRAC SOLUTIONS
Jun 2021 - Nov 2021

EDUCATION

Diploma in Computer Engineering | 2016 - 2019

GOVERNMENT RESIDENTIAL WOMEN'S POLYTECHNIC COLLEGE

• Assured 8.1